Calligraphy
"Calligraphy."
Love and Courage
All right.
Write your favorite word and
submit it by the end of the class.
Effort
Love and
Courage
Favorite word?
What are you gonna write?
Having trouble deciding?
Have you decided what you're gonna write, Такаги-сан?
No... Not yet.
I know. Why don't we write
what we want from each other?
What we want... from each other?
Yep.
Okay.
What I want from Такаги-сан...
Teasing Prohibited
Yeah!
A message telling her not to tease me anymore...
Wait... That might backfire.
Такаги-сан would probably enjoy that.
A word that'll make Такаги-сан
remorseful without provoking her...
This is hard.
You done, Нисиката?
Yeah.
Then, shall we show each other?
Status Quo
Restraint
How's this?
"Restraint"?
Uh, yeah...
Of what? It's something
you want from me, right?
Well, uh... On various things...
Sh-She doesn't get it.
But if she did get it, it'd
have an adverse effect.
This is tricky.
So, what about you?
What do you mean by "status quo"?
Oh, this? It means...
I want Нисиката to stay
the way he is. Easy to tease.
Damn, Такаги-сан is going on the offensive!
I see. So that's how she wants to play this.
I get it now.
Can we do it again?
All right.
Just you watch, Такаги-сан.
I'm gonna go on the offensive this time, too!
Did you finish?
Not yet...
Kindness
With this, I'll make Такаги-сан
realize she isn't very kind.
I hope this will upset you, Такаги-сан.
What should I write...?
Oh? You look uncertain, Такаги-сан.
I believe it's all due to
your lack of kindness.
Oh, by the way, your handwriting is pretty good.
It looks interesting. Did you
learn calligraphy somewhere?
N-No, not really...
Well, I like your handwriting, Нисиката.
Here.
Th-Thanks....
Huh? She's nice all of a sudden...
What's going on...?
Could it be? Is Такаги-сан actually pretty nice,
but I just haven't noticed?!
N-No... That can't be.
Whoa!
Нисиката, stay still for a sec.
Huh?
You had something on your face.
Okay, I thought of a good word.
Running
Grilled Meat
Winning Lawsuit
All right, then.
Show me yours first, Нисиката.
Huh? Not at the same time?
Just show me already.
Don't tease me
I rewrote it, after all.
You really do have interesting handwriting.
Huh?! That's your comment?!
In any case, I want you to stop teasing me.
I can't.
You didn't even consider it.
All right, all right. I'll try my best.
So? What's yours?
Mine?
I wrote... this.
You have ink on your cheek
You did it then!
You just said you'd try your best!
But I did it before I said that.
Don't Let Your Guard Down
Year 1, Class 2, No. 24
Нисиката
Don't Let Your Guard Down
Year 1, Class 2, No. 18
Такаги
Seasonal Change of Clothing
"Seasonal Change of Clothing!"
So hot...
I guess so.
We should change to the
short-sleeve uniform soon.
I guess so.
I should tell Санаэ-тян we should start
wearing our short-sleeve uniforms tomorrow.
I guess so.
You guess what?
Yo.
Aren't you guys hot?
What?
We said we'd all change our
uniforms at the same time!
We did?
We did! You jumped the gun!
I see.
The next day
It's a lot cooler wearing short sleeves!
I guess so.
You guess what?
Санаэ-тян,
good morn... ing...
I thought you said we were all
gonna switch together?
I forgot to tell you.
Legf fe hogh.
"English Translation."
That's right.
Walk down this street to the
post office and turn left there.
You will see the station.
It takes five minutes from here.
I have to get back at Такаги-сан today somehow.
What's the best way to do that?
I haven't made a jack-in-the-box in a while.
No, I don't have enough materials.
Besides, it won't be finished
in time if I start making it now.
All right, let's see...
Нисиката.
Huh? Yes, sir!
Don't "Huh? Yes, sir" me. Hurry up.
It's sixteen.
It's sixteen!
This isn't math class. It's English!
I told you to translate it!
S-Sorry, sir...
Never mind. Sit back down.
I even told you
we're on line sixteen.
Did she intentionally tell me
that so I'd get it wrong?
I didn't think you'd actually get it wrong.
I knew it.
Something on your mind?
You could say that.
What were you thinking?
Oh, it's nothing important.
Then,
were you thinking of something naughty?
Wha?!
N-No!
Really?
Of course not!
Definitely not!
I know.
You were actually thinking how to
get back at me for all the teasing I do, right?
I-I don't know what you're talking about.
I guessed right, didn't I?
You were looking my way, so I kind of figured.
If you knew, then don't ask.
It's fun to see your reactions, though.
And? Did you come up with any good ideas?
Yeah, I did. I came up with the perfect plan.
It's foolproof.
I hope you're right.
She's not worried at all.
Can she see into my mind
and realize I don't have a plan?
So? What's the plan?
A-As if I'd tell you.
Just a hint?
No... Anyway, we should
be paying attention to cla—
June 18th
Today is the eighteenth.
Такаги-сан's student
number is eighteen as well.
If I keep Такаги-сан's
attention away from class,
she might get in trouble for
not knowing where we are in the textbook.
Такаги-сан,
what did you eat for breakfast today?
Mountain yam over rice. Why?
No reason in particular.
So... you like mountain yams?
Yeah, I like them.
I feel energized the entire day
when I eat them in the morning.
I kinda get what you're saying.
What about you, Нисиката?
Me? I...
Take a guess.
Let's see.
Rice.
What do you mean, "rice"?
I didn't peg you as someone
who eats bread. Am I wrong?
No, I did eat rice, but...
It's working! Keep her attention
away from class!
Такаги-сан, you prefer rice, too?
I want someone to read from
the top of the next page.
Hmm... Today is the eighteenth, so...
Такаги.
Here we go!
Well? You don't know where we are, do you?
I will not do such a thing.
Correct.
What?!
Nice try.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Damn, she's good. I wouldn't expect
anything less from Такаги-сан.
I have to come up with another plan.
Maybe I should go on a direct
attack with a jack-in-the-box.
No, again,
I don't have the materials!
Нисиката, what's troubling you?
U-Uh... it's nothing.
Were you thinking about me again?
I-I wouldn't put it that way...
Besides, why would I be thinking about you?
Then you were thinking
about something naughty.
N-No, I wasn't!
I'm always thinking about you, though.
You're blushing.
N-No, I'm not!
You're just thinking about teasing me
like just now, aren't you?
Who knows?
What was that... momentary silence just now?
Today is June eighteenth,
and if I add the month and date
together, it's 24.
Number 24, Нисиката.
Pool
"Pool."
It's the first day we get to go in
the pool, but all I can do is watch.
If it weren't for this injured hand...
No fair. They're all having fun.
Right?
It's the first day of swimming,
and all we can do is watch. It's sad.
T-Такаги-сан, you too?
Yeah.
In your case, is it because
of your hand? What happened?
Ah, yeah...
You know, things happen.
I bet you tried to pet a stray cat
and got bitten, right?
How did you know?! I didn't tell anyone!
I'm actually right?! I just took a wild guess!
What a klutz.
Why are you just observing today—
That reminds me...
A girl who sits out swimming lessons
is usually on her period.
According to the textbook,
it causes abdominal pain.
That's what the King of Health Class, Takao, said...
Ah, it's nothing.
I shouldn't. I don't think it's something
I should be asking, anyway.
You wanted to ask why I'm not swimming today?
She heard me?!
Well, I figured out your reason
is your injured hand,
so why don't you try to guess my reason?
N-Not feeling good.
That's too vague.
No, forget it. I don't really wanna know.
Then I guess I win?
All right, I'll take a guess.
You get one try.
Though I don't think you can guess.
Damn Такаги-сан...
Is she confident because
she thinks I can't say "period"?
If that's the case, she's seriously mocking me!
No, wait!
This is Такаги-сан we're talking about.
It could be a trap!
Even if I gathered my courage and answered...
"Period!"
No, you're so rude!
That's very likely!
But knowing Такаги-сан,
she probably already knows what
I'm thinking and why I'm hesitating.
And then she'll counter that with...
You don't even know the reason
why a girl isn't swimming?
I win, then.
Is it a trap or an honest question?
Is she making it seem genuine
so I'll fall into her trap?
Or is she making it seem like
a trap but asking seriously?
This is all confusing.
Damn it. What was with that
face she made a minute ago?
Other possibilities... Like an injury?
Doesn't seem like it.
It doesn't look like she's feeling
too sick to exercise, either.
Then that would leave... No...
It's not fair. Everyone's having fun.
And I'm over here using all my brain
power battling Такаги-сан in this heat.
Нисиката, are you taking this seriously?
I think you're just looking
at the girls swimming.
N-No, I'm not!
Really?
I heard boys look at girls' chests all the time.
I said I wasn't looking.
I can't say it out loud,
but Такаги-сан doesn't really have a big chest.
I heard that a lot of small-chested girls
are pretty sensitive about it.
That's what the King of
Early Lunch, Kimura, said.
Is Такаги-сан not swimming
because she has a complex about her small chest?!
I knew it. You can't figure it out, can you?
I win today, too.
Такаги-сан, I know why.
You're concerned about
your small chest, right?
There's no way I can say that! It's beyond rude!
In the end, the only answer I have is "period."
But that's plenty rude, too.
You're still thinking? You're almost out of time.
No, it's even mentioned in the textbook.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Yeah, just say it with your head held high!
All right!
The reason why you're sitting out
the swimming lesson
is that...!
You're on your period.
Wrong.
That's rude to say to a girl.
But it's mentioned in our
textbook, and usually, I...
Нисиката, you're bright red.
Then that would mean the reason is that
she has a complex about her small chest?
Too funny.
Upsy-daisy.
By the way, "too embarrassed
because of my small chest"
is also incorrect.
Wha—?!
Sensei,
I changed my mind. May I swim?
Okay.
Huh?
Then why was she watching?
Well then...
Now that I got to see Нисиката make
a good face, I guess I'll go for a swim.
Don't tell me, you were staying out
just to tease me?!
When your hand's all better...
we can swim together.
Oh, it's cold!
I won't fall for it.
When we do swim together,
she's gonna tease me again.
That's the kind of person Такаги-сан is.