Кофе
«Кофе»
Гхе… горький.
Почему такое лицо?
Это разве не кофе?
Мина, но ты же его не любишь.
Ты зачем его купила?
Сейчас я становлюсь взрослой, и думала, что смогу выпить его.
В каком смысле становишься взрослой?
Я вообще-то расту, знаешь ли!
Ты говоришь, что можешь это выпить, Санаэ-тян?
Я могу выпить чёрный.
Чёрный…
Orange с соком
Меняешься?
Но я ведь взрослая.
Три,
два, р—
Меняемся, пожалуйста!
Ура!
Вкуснотища…
А так разве можно?
Ну, полно взрослых, которые не пьют кофе.
Ты всё ещё ребёнок.
Э! Злюка!
Вах…
Ах, ты ж…
Взрослые так не поступают.
Apple Tea
As usual, Такаги-сан made fun of me a lot today.
But tomorrow, I'll…
Нисиката.
Такаги-сан!
Huh?
Are you alone today?
Ah, yeah.
Then, let's walk home together.
Huh? Why?
What?
Uh… It's nothing.
But you're on your bike.
I'll just push.
Empty Can
"Empty Can."
That's a new drink that came out recently, right?
Is it good?
What is this? Is this some kind of a trap?
It's good. You want a sip?
Can I?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh…
I don't really mind, but isn't this…
an indirect kiss?
How's that, Такаги-сан?
It's embarrassing, right?! Be embarrassed!
Wh-What?!
She's not embarrassed at all!
What is up with her?!
Here. Thanks. It's good.
You're not gonna drink it?
No, I'm gonna drink it, of course.
It's nothing. This is nothing.
It's an indirect kiss.
What are you doing?
Uhh… Where's a trash can?
Damn it…
Wow! Nice shot, Нисиката.
I threw it without thinking.
I didn't expect to make it.
I had no idea I had such talent.
All right. I wanna try.
What are you aiming at?
You weren't even close, Такаги-сан!
How about a match, then?
A match?
I don't mind. I won't lose, though.
Then, we'll throw one at a time.
The first one to make it wins.
To challenge me to a match she can't win…
Такаги-сан has lost her cool!
This feels great.
If you win, I'll do anything you want me to do.
I heard that loud and clear.
You better not take it back later.
I won't.
Though, there's no way I'm gonna lose.
Here I go!
Hup!
If you miss, I win.
She… She tricked me yet again.
Stand at the same place and the same angle.
Okay.
I can do this. I can definitely do this.
Oh, yeah.
If you win…
I'll give you my first kiss.
I guess I win.
That wasn't fair.
What wasn't fair?
"What wasn't fair"? When I was throwing it, you…
What?
Nothing…
A promise is a promise.
What should I make you do?
What? What's coming?
But…
I guess I don't mind if you don't do anything.
But, Такаги-сан, that's…
If you do that, I'll feel like
I can never win against you.
You can't win, so what's the problem?
Huh? What is that supposed to mean?
Hey!
Soda
"Soda."
Ughh… It's spicy.
What's with that face?
Ramune
You're drinking soda.
I thought you don't like soda, Мина.
Why are sodas so spicy?
Why do you always buy drinks you don't like?
Pretending to be an adult again?
No. It's because I love the flavor.
It hurts!
My tongue! My tongue!
So annoying…
It hurts your tongue when
you drink soda, right, Юкари-тян?
Nope.
Then you try it!
All right.
You'll definitely feel the pain.
It won't.
You feel it, don't you? Tell the truth.
Nope.
What pain is she talking about?
It'll never come.
Oh no. I'm about to burp.
You feel it, don't you?
If I burp now, she's gonna make fun of me.
Oh, but I can't…
hold it any longer.
There it is again!
Wh-What?
Nothing.
Here it comes!
See you tomorrow!
Just you wait, Такаги-сан.
Including including the walk home,
she teased me fifteen times in total today.
When I make a mistake during the game,
I train ten times harder for
each mistake as punishment.
I believe that will lead to my next victory.
That's it!
She teased me fifteen times,
so ten times that is one 150!
That seems a bit too much for the first time.
L-Let's do three times for now!
One, two, three…
Eighteen,
nineteen…
twenty…
This is a lot harder than I thought.
Maybe I shouldn't do so many. No, I have to!
This is my punishment for
getting teased so many times!
I'll relish this agony
and heighten my motivation
to get back at her next time!
Go, me!
Muscle Training
"Muscle Training."
Something wrong with your arms?
Are you hurt?
Uh, no. Just sore from training.
Stop it! It really hurts!
Does that count as one?
I should keep myself accountable,
so that'll count as one.
Made you flinch!
You must be really sore.
That was definitely teasing.
So, why are you sore all of a sudden?
I started muscle training yesterday.
I hope you won't quit after three days.
Go ahead. Make fun, Такаги-сан.
Why…?
Такаги-сан teased me twenty-three times today.
That's more than yesterday!
One, two, three…
I just remembered.
Are you still training, Нисиката?
Uh, yeah.
So you didn't quit after three days.
Thanks to you.
Oh, but did you know?
Know what?
They say if you train too much
during your growth spurt,
it'll stop you from getting taller.
Wait. I think I did hear
that somewhere before.
That's not good!
If Такаги-сан grows taller than me,
she'll make fun of me even more!
What should I do? What should I do?!
Apparently that's just a rumor, though.
A rumor?!
In fact, moderate exercise
actually supports your growth.
So, that being the case, you should
continue to train without worrying.
I think it's a good thing.
You kind of look a tiny bit more muscular.
You think?
What's wrong? You're all quiet.
Don't tell me you're blushing.
I'm not blushing.
Your face is red.
You're definitely blushing.
Why do you always tease me every day?
Because you make priceless reactions.
Besides, I wasn't lying
about you looking muscular.
You're kind of looking good lately.
You're even more red now.
No, it's because it's hot!
Hey, Такаги-сан!
That was fifty-four today.
Oh, fifty-five including this one.
But, I think I'll continue to train
even if Такаги-сан doesn't tease me.
Dubbing
"Dubbing."
Johnny-сан, are you eating
dinner at home tonight?
Well, that depends on work.
If it gets too late, I'll just eat with
Jirou on my way home, yeah?
It's good you're close with Jirou-сан,
but you should have dinner at home sometimes.
I'm starting to feel lonely, ya know?
Yeah, but it's work.
Let's go home already.
Huh? Just a bit longer, yeah?
Why are you talking in Kansai dialect?
So annoying…
You're horrible! I'm not important to you, am I?!
That's not fair, Hanako.
I'm trying my best here, yeah?
Why are you crying, darling?
Because… it's as if Jirou-сан and
your work took you away from me.
I don't think I can take this any longer.
It's getting intense.
Oh, jeez. What a pain!
How terrible! That's an awful
thing to say, Johnny-сан!
If you're gonna act like that,
I'm gonna do this, too!
Hey…
They're both male.
Hey, it's Johnny-senpai!
Oh, it's you, Jirou! You wanna go grab a bite?
Can we just go home already?
Umbrella
"Umbrella."
Ugh, it starts raining right when school ends.
No one told me it was gonna rain!
I didn't bring my raincoat!
You dummy.
Санаэ, don't be so mean to Мина.
You want to take the bus home, then?
I don't have any bus money!
Dumber than dumb.
Stop that.
I'll lend you bus fare.
Damn it… I got teased a lot today, too.
Aren't you going home, Такаги-сан?
Well, I didn't bring either
a raincoat or umbrella.
You're such an airhead, Такаги-сан!
You didn't know it was gonna
rain today? What an airhead!
No comeback…?
Your umbrella is pretty big, isn't it?
Huh?
Don't we look like a couple under an umbrella?
How did this happen?!
This isn't good. This is really awkward.
What should I do?
Just talk about anything.
Такаги-сан, what are you gonna do with your bike?
I'll walk to school tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
This is starting to feel
really embarrassing now.
It's hard to breathe.
I need to distract myself somehow.
Такаги-сан.
Well?!
Be surprised, Такаги-сан!
How cute.
Say what?!
Damn… That's Такаги-сан
for you. This is nothing to her.
Slurp?
You're way too freaked out!
Hey, Нисиката, is your
other shoulder getting wet?
Just a little bit. It's fine.
No, it's not. You're going to catch a cold.
I'm going to scoot closer,
so get yourself under the umbrella.
M-My heart's pounding… so fast!
Calm down.
If Такаги-сан finds out I'm nervous,
she's gonna make fun of me again!
Just talk about something!
Такаги-сан.
It's not like you to forget your umbrella.
Could it be that you're actually an airhead?
Was that too harsh?
I guess I can be a little forgetful.
Такаги-сан admitted she's forgetful?!
What an occasion! I feel like I've won!
I'm having trouble
remembering something right now, actually.
Really? Like what?
This situation we're in right now, with
two of us under the same umbrella…
What was the word for it?
I can't seem to remember.
Uh… Umm…
What was it called again?
Aiaigasa.
Huh? What?
I can't hear you.
Oh, I remember!
It's Aiaigasa.
There's no way you forgot that!
Oh, and what do you call that thing
where a couple presses their lips
together to express their love?
Dammit, I lose if I don't answer!
K-Kiss…
I can't hear you because of the rain.
It's not raining that hard anymore.
Don't pretend you didn't hear.
It's a k-kiss.
Oh, that's right.
And how about that phrase a couple says
to each other to express their feelings?
You know, the one that
goes beyond "I like you."
It starts with an "A"…
H-How should I know?
Then comes "I."
I-I don't know.
Then, how about in English?
"I"…
What comes after that?
"I lo"…
Next letter?
Say it.
That's enough.
Last word is "you."
Come on.
Oh, jeez.
The rain stopped.
You're right.
I'm saved.
I was sweating just thinking she was gonna
keep it up until we reached her house.
O-Okay, then. My house is this
way, so see you later, Такаги-сан.
I forgot how to get home.
Jeez, give me a break!