Congrats to Boys' Volleyball!
Congrats to Girls' Tennis on
entering the prefectural tournament!
Hey, Нисиката.
You've been too loud during class lately.
You better shape up.
Y-Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
I'm putting you in charge of cleaning
the science room after school.
Huh?
Staff meeting notes
Student from my class on
cleaning duty for science room:
Нисиката
Make sure you wipe the desks clean, too.
Huh?!
Cleaning Duty
"Cleaning Duty."
Science Room
Why only me?
Такаги-сан is at fault, too.
She's the one who's always
teasing me during class.
I guess it's my reactions
that are loud.
Let's just get this over with and go home—
T-Такаги-сан?!
You're so surprised!
This was worth having
to stay and wait for a while.
T-Такаги-сан, do you have to clean
the room as punishment, too?
Let's just get it over with.
Y-Yeah...
So, I have a suggestion.
If we have to clean,
we should turn it into a game so it's fun.
A game?
Yep.
We'll do rock-paper-scissors
and the loser has to clean
a quarter of the room. You in?
In other words, if I win four times,
I don't have to do anything.
Okay.
All right. First round.
I'm going with rock.
She's declaring it?!
You ready?
Rock?! So if I go with paper, I'll win?
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
But, wait!
I told you I was going with rock!
Damn it!
You need to trust me more.
Then I'll just trust her word next time.
By the way, I'm not going to
declare anything anymore.
Damn...
Isn't she teasing me again?
Нисиката.
Накай-кун.
What are you two doing here?
I was loud during class, so I have
to clean the room as punishment.
That's rough.
What are you doing?
Oh, me?
I was just hanging around.
I see.
Накай-кун, we shouldn't get in their way.
Oh, yeah.
We'll get going, then.
Ah, okay. See you.
Oh, and Нисиката...
Good luck!
Huh? Oh,
cleaning?
Let's go.
Sorry, Такаги-тян.
No worries. See you.
Did you know?
The two of them are going out.
Huh?! Seriously?!
I had no idea.
I mean, I did notice they're
hanging out a lot together, but...
It's not as though they're hiding it, but
they're both not the type to announce it.
Yeah.
He said they're just hanging around,
but they were on their way to the rooftop.
The rooftop?
Right about now, it's probably
just the two of them on the rooftop...
Just the two of them...
Are you cleaning?
Ah, yeah! I'm cleaning!
Man, they're enjoying their youth.
Just the two of them. Enjoying their youth...
I wonder...
I wonder what it's like.
To enjoy your youth.
Right?
N-No idea...
I-I'm done.
Okay, then...
Rock, paper...
I ended up losing all four times.
Phew, we're finally done!
Let's go home, Нисиката.
Jeez... I hope you learn from
this and stop teasing me.
I guess I can be more discreet.
We're gonna get punished again!
When it happens, it happens.
Huh?!
Besides, I wasn't told
to clean in the first place.
Huh?! Are you serious?!
Why am I the only one who
gets in trouble all the time?
So you're just here to tease me.
That too, but...
I wanted to
enjoy my youth, too.
E—
Enjoy youth...
Нисиката, you're buying me
juice on our way home.
What? Why?!
Kickover
"Kickover."
So hot...
I'm thirsty.
I know. Want to compete on something?
Loser buys drinks.
Okay.
Can I decide what to compete on, then?
A high bar?
The one who can't do
a kickover on the high bar loses.
I just casually tried a kickover
on the high bar recently...
and surprise! I succeeded
for the first time in my life.
Since then, I've been waiting for
Такаги-сан to challenge me to a duel.
Maybe Такаги-сан is able to do it, too.
But!
Hey, Нисиката.
I'm wearing a skirt.
Exactly!
She can't do a kickover wearing a skirt!
She's unable to compete!
Oh, well.
Then, can I go first?
R-Really?
Really.
But you have to turn the other
way when I'm doing it.
Huh?!
I am wearing a skirt, after all.
If you look while I'm doing
a kickover, you lose.
Here I go.
Okay, your turn next.
Really? Did she really do it?
No, I should save my breath.
For now, just concentrate!
Wow.
We both did it. What now?
Let's do it again.
Okay.
I'll go first again.
Didn't even hesitate.
Very confident, aren't you?
She's not even worried she'll fail this time?
I bet she probably
isn't actually doing a kickover.
She said I'd lose if I look her way,
but it's a different story if she's cheating.
I'll finally win today!
No way! She's actually doing it!
Shorts?!
Нисиката, you can look now.
What's wrong?
Sorry, Такаги-сан...
I lose.
Here.
Thanks.
Though, I don't really feel like I won
since you lost on your own.
But if you had shorts on, I didn't
have to look the other way.
Pervert.
Y-You're wrong!
I just wanted to check if you were
actually doing a kickover!
Really?
Really!
You thought I was cheating, then?
Huh? No, I mean...
100% Unrequited Love
Hmph!
What is wrong with you?!
You're always picking on me!
It's nothing.
Heart-thump!
But you don't hate
this kind of thing, do you?
Squeal!
You don't hate
this kind of thing, do you?
Squeal!
100% Unrequited Love...
Cold
"Cold."
Listen, I'll say it again.
This will be on the test.
Make sure you remember.
Good morning...
Нисиката,
Yes, I think so.
Morning. You have a cold?
Yeah.
It's nothing. No big deal.
Nailed it!
It's because you stayed up late
watching 100% Unrequited Love.
How did she know?!
Squeal, squeal!
You're too loud, Такаги-sa—
Ow!
You're the one being loud!
S-Sorry, sir.
That was mean, Такаги-сан.
Are you okay, Нисиката?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Damn it. She's ruthless even when I'm sick!
But! I have the ultimate secret plan today!
What's an outsider like him doing here?!
Now I'm mad! I'm going to
give him a piece of my mind!
Excuse me!
Hmph!
You're cute.
S-Squeal!
I can use this!
I may have caught a cold, but that's
nothing compared to what I've acquired!
Okay, Такаги-сан. Hit me with your best shot!
I'll counter it and make you blush!
Ni—
Come at me anytime!
What?
It's nothing.
Odd. Why isn't she making her move?
I can't keep this pose forever.
I can't even write what's on the board.
Is it possible that she figured
it out from this pose?!
That I'm gonna counter her?!
What if I sit normally?
How's this?
Wh-What's wrong with you, Такаги-сан?!
She'd usually have
teased me three times by now.
Is she sick or something?
When Такаги-сан's quiet, she's...
Oh, no...
I'm starting to feel embarrassed
about saying "You're cute!" as my counter.
I couldn't even say it to begin
with! How stupid am I?!
It's probably due to lack
of sleep and being sick.
Is something wrong, Нисиката?
I-It's nothing.
Your face is a little red.
Huh?
Are you okay? You look tired.
I... I'm okay. Really.
But you're turning red. Do you have a fever?
Why are you so nice to me today, Такаги-сан?!
No, really. It's nothing.
Really?
Yeah, really!
When I said I caught a cold,
it was more like an excuse!
It was already eight-thirty
by the time I woke up,
so that's why I was late! I'm really fine!
So you're okay.
Yeah, I'm totally fine!
I can tease you, then.
What do you mean by that?!
She ended up making fun of me
more than usual that day.
Squeal, squeal!
Hey, Юкари-тян, Санаэ-тян! Hurry, hurry!
Why are we doing this just for a popsicle?
It's a baked sweet potato flavored popsicle!
It's only available in the summer!
Baked sweet potato in the summer?
It's sold out everywhere, but
I think a snack store would have it.
So hurry, hurry!
What are you doing, Юкари-тян?!
We're taking a shortcut!
Такаги-сан and Нисиката-кун
are at the snack store.
Snacks / Toys
Oh, you're right.
Is it possible that they're...
Мина, we shouldn't get in their way—
Hey, Такаги-тян!
Tailing
"Tailing."
Baked Sweet Potato Flavored Popsicle
Found it! Baked sweet
potato flavored popsicle!
Ice Cream
G-Good for you...
See you tomorrow.
Lucky...
Lucky how?
You know. That relationship
between a man and a woman...
Huh?! Why?!
You didn't see it?
You're the one who started it.
Hey, why are we following them?
We live the opposite way.
Shh! They're going to see us!
So, what do you think?
Do you feel something, watching those two?
Hmm...
Oh! They have a bike,
so why don't they ride it together?
Right?! Riding a bike together after school!
Oh, but you can be together
longer if you walk home.
Maybe the bike has a flat tire?
It's so hard to choose!
That's it.
Can I have a bite?
Just one bite.
Такаги-сан, wanna race?
Race?
Yeah, we'll start once we turn that corner.
The first one to the shrine wins.
Okay, I guess.
Такаги-сан has a flat tire.
There's no doubt I'm gonna be faster.
There's no way they're saying that!
What do you mean "race"?!
They must be talking about
something more sensual than that.
Hey, Нисиката, I don't mind
racing you to the shrine,
but before we do that...
They're gone?!
Did they get to the shrine already?
So fast!
Did they find out we were tailing them?
Hey, let's go home already.
Ah, yeah...
Let's go buy some more popsicles.
Give me a bite.
So close...
Are they gone?
Wh-Why were they following us?
Who knows.
Shouldn't we just have turned the next corner?
See? It's right there.
Now that you mention it...
Would you have preferred that?
Ah, I guess it wouldn't have mattered.
Okay. Good.
Oh, yeah. We were going
to race to the shrine, right?
Ready, go!
Huh?
H-Hey!
That's a false start, Такаги-сан!
Anyway, tailing them was fun.
We just took the long way home.
Maybe they did find out.
I better apologize to Такаги-сан tomorrow.
They're out of the baked
sweet potato flavored popsicles!
Delicious Red Bean Soup Popsicle with Mochi
Oh, well. I'll just get the red bean soup flavor!
Shouldn't you get something more
appropriate for the season?
Can I have a bite?