С меня хватит!
I can't study for the test any longer!
Let's go to the arcade.
If you say so, I guess we have to.
Hey, let's go, Нисиката.
You'll get stupid if you study too much.
No, I'll study.
I see!
See ya!
Let's go play!
Which bishoujo figure are you getting?
Damn it... I'm jealous.
But! I have to get a good grade
on my next test!
Hey, can I sit here?
Studying for the test?
Ah, yeah...
Studying for the Test
"Studying for the Test."
I passed by Такао-кун
and the others just now.
Yeah. We were all studying together.
Night on the Galactic Railroad
They were running out of here
yelling, "Let's go play!"
You aren't going with them?
I don't have time to play.
If I don't score within the top
fifty of my grade,
my parents are gonna
confiscate my video games.
Hmm, I see.
Oh, no! Why am I telling her everything?!
If I give her that info, she'll definitely
interfere with my studying!
J-Just kidding...
About what?
It's nothing.
A-Anyway, no interruptions...
That's mean. You say that like
I'm always getting in your way or something.
Y-You are!
That's because...
it's fun to tease you, Нисиката.
Should I study somewhere else?
No, if I do that, it'll be like
I've let Такаги-сан win.
You're not studying, Такаги-сан?
Yeah. I have a rule about
studying only two hours a day.
I see.
I didn't expect anything less from Такаги-сан.
She can easily score in
the top ten of our grade.
But... what is she thinking?
This is Такаги-сан we're talking about,
I'm sure she's gonna do
something to get in my way.
There's no way she won't.
Because she's Такаги-сан!
What?
Ah, it's nothing.
I guess it's nothing.
I was just looking. It's not like—
Oh, that one is wrong.
Huh?
Problem six, where it says
"Solve for x over (-2 + 3y)."
Huh? I got this wrong?
Yeah.
How?
Where? This is, uhh...
Here we go.
Такаги-сан?
It's easier for me to teach you this way.
So, x equals -16 and y equals -1, right?
Такаги-сан is teaching me?!
First, just substitute them as-is.
What is she planning?!
Write out the formula.
Ah, okay...
This will be a negative number
times a negative number,
so pay attention to the
order of operations.
Oh! Then, the answer is...
five.
Yep, that's right.
Oh, and this...
Такаги-сан is amazing. She can
figure it out at just a quick glance.
Th-Thanks... I wasn't really getting this.
Okay, I'll just teach you from
the beginning, then.
T-Такаги-сан is gonna teach me?
I'm saved!
No, something's fishy!
Why is she being so nice?! It's odd!
T-Такаги-сан, why are you
being so nice to me today?
What do you mean?
Well, you're kinda being
unusually nice today, so...
Yeah... I'm always teasing you during class,
so I'd feel bad if your grades go down
because of me.
Нисиката...
I'm sorry for teasing you every day.
Let's make sure you do well on the next test.
Такаги-сан...
You've finally changed your ways!
All right! I'll do my best!
Thanks for the juice.
No, thank you.
I made huge progress
on math today, thanks to you.
I have a better chance
of not getting my games confiscated.
Maybe Такаги-сан is actually a good person.
Seriously, thanks for today, Такаги-сан.
You don't need to thank me.
After all, what I taught you today
won't be on the test.
H-Hey, wait!
You've mastered substitution, right?
I did, but still!
Give me back that juice!
Oh, I opened it already.
You just opened it now!
Test
"Test."
Pass the answer sheets forward.
I think I did well. I should've gotten
a ninety, at least.
Good, good.
Юкари-тян...
Can you teach this to me?
English is not my cup of tea.
Huh? You make it sound as though
you're good at everything else.
I meant it's my worst subject!
Anyway, the translation for this—
Sorry, but I want to review as well.
Huh?! But you always help me study!
If I get ninety percent or above
on all the tests this time,
my parents will buy any video game I want!
How do I turn this into a negative sentence?
Were you listening?!
In any case, I don't have
the time to teach you guys!
Meanie!
Which is more important?
A video game or friends?!
Yeah, yeah.
You can play video games, but
but you can't teach a video game!
Right, right.
Now that those nuisances
are gone, I should review.
All right, I'm handing out the test now.
Pass it back.
Okay, I've thoroughly reviewed
the subject before the test.
Everyone got one?
I'll score above ninety percent
on this English test as well!
First-year End of Term Test
Math
Math?!
Test Results
"Test Results."
Here.
Did you study at all?
Next, Saitou.
You look worried.
Not really...
Такаги.
Yes, sir.
You did well, as usual.
Такаги-тян, what did you get?
Can I see the answers later?
Y-You got a good score?
Yeah, but not a hundred percent.
That's Такаги-сан for you. But I should—
Next, Нисиката!
Yes, sir!
Do a little better next time, will ya?
Was it bad?
As if you're so concerned!
You're the one who taught me
stuff not covered on the test.
You say that so casually only
because you got a good score!
Hey. I said, hey.
Let's try to guess each other's score.
Whoever guesses closer wins.
You always do stuff
like this out of the blue.
I guess I don't mind.
Umm... About fifty percent?
You underestimate me too much, Такаги-сан.
I see.
Then, did you get above sixty percent?
So it's below that.
How did she know?!
Give her your poker face!
Confuse her with your poker face!
Did you get above fifty-five percent?
It is.
Why?!
So it's between fifty-five to fifty-nine.
I have to stop her from
guessing the exact score.
Okay, then...
Fifty-six.
Fifty-seven?
Fifty-eight?
Fifty-nine?
Hmm, I got it.
It's fifty-six percent.
Is that your answer, Такаги-сан?
Yep.
My test score is...
fifty-nine percent!
Sucks for you!
You were close, though.
The only thing that sucks
is your test score.
You're right, sir.
Aww, I was off by three?
You guess my score now.
If you're off within two percent, you win.
Okay! I'm gonna figure it out
based on Такаги-сан's reaction!
The teacher praised her, so
it must be above ninety percent.
Then, is it around ninety-two percent?
What was that reaction?
Is it above ninety-five?
Ninety?
Ninety-two?
She's faking it! I'm not gonna fall for it!
Такаги-сан would never make
her reaction so obvious!
Damn, she's mocking me.
I'm gonna do everything
within my power to win this!
Focus more on her expression.
Wh-What?
Oh, it's nothing. It's just that
we've been staring at each
other for a while now.
Why are you turning away?
That's a cheap shot, Такаги-сан!
I can't look at you after you said that!
Think... Just think... A hint of some sort...
To make such a fake reaction,
it must mean Такаги-сан wants me
to think she got ninety-two percent!
That also means it won't be
between ninety and ninety-four,
since they're within a two-percent difference!
Furthermore, the teacher praised
her, so it's above ninety percent.
And it's not a hundred percent, so...
it's between ninety-five and ninety-nine!
It's flawless! Perfect victory!
Такаги-сан, you scored...
ninety-seven percent!
Wrong. I got ninety-two percent.
Wh-What?!
You don't trust me enough.
I gave you a three-point handicap
on purpose for nothing.
Bookstore
"Bookstore."
100% Unrequited Love
Fierce!!
Ultimate Soccer!!
Books
No one's coming. No one's coming.
Welcome.
It'll be 420 yen, ple—
Exactly 420 yen.
Would you like a cover—
No, thank you.
Would you like a bag—
A rece—
No, thank you.
I got it!
Now, all I have to do is take
this home and read it—
Morning, Нисиката.
T-Такаги-сан? Why is she here?!
I'm taking a walk.
Did she just read my mind?!
What are you doing, Нисиката?
Crap... If she sees this...
I have to play dumb no matter what.
Well, uh... I wanted to buy a book,
but they were all out—
Wait, wait! Maybe she saw me at the register!
I-I bought volume eleven of
Fierce!! Ultimate Soccer!!
How's that?
It's popular among boys, but girls
aren't interested in that series at all.
It's a perfect answer!
I'm on a roll today—
Fierce-Soccer? Let me see. Let me see!
Huh?
Uh, but... I haven't read it yet.
Can I at least see the cover?
No, no! Definitely no!
I haven't had the chance to look at it, either.
Then, let's look at it together.
I like to look at it alone!
Aww...
I had no idea she'd be this interested.
Such a dangerous person...
I better get away from her quick.
See you later, Такаги-сан.
Um...
We coincidentally ran into each other.
Why don't we walk together for a bit?
"Coincidentally"?
You don't always run into
someone at a bookstore
this far from home so
early in the morning.
But to think there's something in
this backpack I can't let her see,
it's as though my heart's in my mouth.
I wish I were home already.
Hey, Нисиката.
Are you lying to me?
Are you lying?
Uh, um...
You didn't buy Fierce-Soccer, did you?
You bought something so
embarrassing you had to lie about it?
No... Uh...
It's just a girl's manga, right?
100% Unrequited Love?
No, I mean, that is what I got...
But how did you know?!
Well, I just happened to be passing by
when I saw you at the register,
and I saw the title as well.
She knew it all along and was playing with me.
Is it because you like the anime?
I didn't know you read that kind of stuff.
Uh, Такаги-сан!
Please don't tell anyone.
Watching it on TV is one thing,
but if people found out I'm actually
buying and reading the manga,
I'll be a laughingstock.
Hmm, should I? I mean, you did lie to me.
I've never lied to you, you know.
All right, I won't tell.
Huh?
That easily?
What?
I'm serious. Seriously, don't tell anyone.
Okay.
Seriously?! That was too easy, Такаги-сан!
You're so persistent...
Oh, then how about this?
I'll tell you my secret.
You'll be somewhat at ease
knowing my secret, too, right?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
Then, lean closer.
Uh, okay.
I like you, Нисиката.
Huh?
Huh?! Такаги-сан? Huh?!
You're bright red!
You blush so quickly, Нисиката.
Since you lied to me,
I lied to you as payback.
Oh, a lie... You startled me.
Yep, a lie.
Of course I'm lying.
I'm going this way, so see you.
Right. Bye-bye, see you.
A lie, huh?
Oh, Нисиката.
I want to read 100% Unrequited Love
too, so can I borrow it next time?
Don't say it out loud, Такаги-сан!
Shelter from the Rain
"Shelter from the Rain."
It started raining so suddenly.
I wonder if it's going to stop soon.
Hmm, I don't know...
Aww, even my socks got wet.
How about you, Нисиката?
I-I can kinda see through, Такаги-сан!
Are you listening?
Uh, yeah, right...
Keep calm! Keep calm!
If she realizes I'm panicking,
I'll be branded as a pervert!
Yeah, I hope it'll stop soon.
I wanna go home soon because there's
an anime I wanna watch past five.
It's Fierce-Soccer, by the way.
The one you bought at the bookstore?
Oh, wait. That was 100% Unrequited Love.
Y-You promised you wouldn't say anything!
But I can talk to you about it, right?
You're the person in question, after all.
I hope it stops soon.
Uhh, yeah...
Aww, it's a little wet.
Hey, Нисиката. Do you have your P.E. shirt?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
Can I borrow it? I'll wash
it and return it to you.
I want to change out of this.
Change out of it? To my P.E. shirt? Here?
Yeah. My shirt's wet. I feel gross.
But...
Besides, it seems like you're having
trouble deciding where to look.
She noticed.
Can you turn the other way?
Y-Yeah...
You managed to stay pretty dry, huh?
Yeah.
How?
Oh, you used your bag as an umbrella?
Y-Yeah...
I see. I had to hold my bike.
Right...
You can look if you want.
Uh, Такаги-сан? What are you say—
I'm done changing.
Why are you flustered?
She's toying with me!
Hey, you want to make a bet
on whether or not the rain will stop
by the time the town clock strikes five?
The loser has to do
anything the winner wants.
Okay.
What's your bet?
The rain won't stop.
Then, I'll bet the rain will stop.
If the rain stops, I can go home
and watch Fierce-Soccer.
If the rain doesn't stop,
I get to order Такаги-сан around.
I win either way!
I feel better now that I've changed my shirt.
Thanks, Нисиката.
Don't mention it.
It smells kinda sweaty, though.
It's summer. Of course it does!
The fabric that was on my body
is touching Такаги-сан's.
No! What am I thinking?!
A cat...
Oh, hey.
Are you here to take shelter?
Come here.
He's cute, but be careful.
He scratches.
You want your shirt back?
No, I'm fine.
Why don't you wear my P.E. shirt?
Huh?
It's a little wet, but it's better
than what you're wearing.
The fabric that was touching
Такаги-сан's body will be...
You done changing?
Don't look! Jeez!
I feel as if I'm doing something naughty.
It smells good.
I guess I win.
What should I make you do?
Oh, well. Fierce-Soccer will be
waiting for me when I get home.
Let's just get this over with
and run home.
Hey, Нисиката.
It stopped raining, so let's go
somewhere before we go home.
But Такаги-сан, I...
You promised the loser
would obey, right? Let's go!
Aww...