Attendance
Well, summer vacation starts tomorrow,
but don't go too crazy. Got it?
Hey,
let's go to the beach tomorrow.
Good idea.
I suddenly have a craving for watermelon!
What's up with that?
Let's spit the seeds.
Yeah!
Tandem
Riding
"Tandem riding."
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
Yeah, the long-awaited
summer vacation is finally here!
With no school, I can play as much as I want!
You better do your homework.
I bet you're planning
not to do it tomorrow,
because it's only the
first day of vacation.
How did you know?!
So I'm right?
B-But we have to enjoy summer vacation.
I wanna go to the pool and
the beach, and go camping and stuff.
Summer vacation is way too short!
I wish we could have summer vacation forever!
Really?
I like school, too.
Because...
it's fun.
Summer vacation, huh?
So hot!
The breeze feels good.
We need more speed!
No way, it's way too hot.
So hot...
Should we do what they were doing?
Huh?!
You go in the front, of course.
No, we shouldn't!
It's dangerous with the cars and stuff.
There are no cars here,
and it's not a public road.
But...
Oh? Could it be that you're embarrassed?
N-No, that's not it!
Oh, so you can't do it, then.
What are you saying? Tandem riding is easy.
It's just that we shouldn't do it
because it's dangerous.
Let's go to the vacant lot, then.
Huh?
If you can't do it, you owe me juice.
Just you watch, Такаги-сан.
Tandem riding is nothing!
That one doesn't count!
I can do this!
Juice it is, then.
Wait, wait!
T-Tandem riding is this hard?!
Такаги-сан, you're not throwing us
off balance on purpose, are you?
Nope.
Are you sure?
I'm just sitting how I usually sit.
If we can't do it, it's all
because of you, Нисиката.
Because when I did this last time,
the person in front was able
to peddle smoothly.
R-Really? That's great.
A girl... friend of yours?
Nope. Not a girl.
Oh...
One more time. I've almost got it.
Whoa!
I'll get it this time!
Damn... I feel frustrated for some reason!
What is this?
Are you getting aggressive?
No, I'm not!
I just don't want to buy you juice!
Yeah, I just don't want to
buy her a drink. That's all!
Oh, we're moving.
By the way, Нисиката,
the last time I went tandem riding,
It was with my dad.
Huh?
I think I was four years old at the time.
Here.
Thanks.
Tasty!
Нисиката, you're not getting a drink?
Uh, yeah...
I'll pass.
I can't tell her I have no money to buy my own.
Grape Cider
You want some?
No... thanks.
She's gonna say it's an indirect kiss
or whatever and make fun of me again!
Don't kid yourself. Have a sip.
I really don't want any.
Endure it.
I need to endure it.
Here, you're going to get heatstroke.
Huh? I-I can have it?
Yeah,
because...
you get too embarrassed
about an indirect kiss.
Th-That's not it!
Really?
R-Really!
I-It's so hot.
Thanks for the drink.
We won't be walking home
from school for a while.
Well, yeah. It's summer vacation.
I know.
Starting from tomorrow, let's practice
tandem riding here until noon.
Huh?
I guess it's okay. But not on the road.
Yeah, we'll just ride here.
If we're only riding here, there's
no point in practicing, don't you think?
No, there is.
Summer vacation starts tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Well, then! Let's go home.
Summer vacation, huh?
I can't wait for summer vacation.
You're saying that now?
First
Day of
Summer
Vacation
"First Day of Summer Vacation."
To think it would rain on the first
day of summer vacation...
My summer vacation plans are ruined!
It's just for a day. Who cares?
I was supposed to go to the pool today.
I'm never getting the time back!
Stop crying.
There's nothing we can do about the rain.
Let's start our homework.
Huh?
What do you mean, "Huh?"
Don't tell me you didn't bring your homework.
I told you we should do our homework since
we can't do anything because of the rain!
I thought I misheard you.
Why?!
Why do we have homework during
summer vacation in the first place?!
Don't you think that's wrong?!
We can't have a vacation during vacation.
Right?
But we do have homework,
so we have to do it.
Oh, jeez! Юкари-тян,
quit doing your homework and relax!
Doing your homework in front of me
reminds me of homework,
and I can't enjoy myself!
Not my problem!
You should be reminded of homework!
It's only the first day.
Just forget about homework.
That's typical of a person who will be
crying with regret on August 31st.
You're so stubborn!
I'm just gonna read manga, so there.
100% Unrequited Love
Whatever...
Юкари-тян...
Can we write our book report on manga?
That's it!
Can you two just go home?
Test of Courage
"Test of Courage."
Good, it stopped raining.
Wait, why am I happy about that?
Нисиката.
You're here.
Yeah, we made a promise.
I guess so.
Is something wrong?
Uh, n-no... It's nothing.
Wow, so many puddles.
It really poured last night, huh?
I didn't recognize her for a second there.
Come to think of it, I ran into her
coincidentally a few times on our days off,
but this is our first time meeting up.
Could this be what people call a date?!
No, no! That's not what this is!
We're just practicing tandem riding.
Нисиката.
Wh-What is it?
Were you listening?
S-Sorry, what did you say?
We can't tandem ride in this condition.
Uh, yeah...
I was planning to go out in the
afternoon right after our practice.
It's a pain to go back home, so will
you hang out with me to kill some time?
I-Is this... a date?!
No, no, no, no...
I guess so. But someplace
where there aren't many people.
There's no telling what our classmates
would say if any of them saw us.
Hmm...
Then... How about...
A test of courage?
Perfect for summer, right?
Isn't it usually done at night?
Don't worry. I heard it's really dark in there.
Besides, people say there's a presence here.
What presence?
This tunnel goes straight,
but a lot of cars crashed into
the walls for some reason,
so they had to make a new
road beside it instead.
Ever since, the bloodthirsty
ghosts appear every night
in search of cars to prey upon.
But that's not all.
Around here, there's a rumor
about being spirited away.
Sometimes, people suddenly disappear.
Aren't you going in?
Don't tell me you're scared.
N-No way!
It's only noon right now.
There's no way I'm scared!
It's... way darker than I thought.
The breeze is making an odd noise.
Hey, check this out.
A paper talisman?
It's to ward off evil spirits.
That must mean there's something evil here.
Нисиката's scared.
N-No, I'm not! That was only—
Look...
N-Now what?
What's this steel barrel doing here?
Wh-Who knows?
Check what's inside, Нисиката.
Huh?
You scared?
I'm not scared! I'll look!
I'll check it out, all right?
What's the big idea, Такаги-сан—
Такаги-сан? Huh?
Такаги-сан? Where are you?
Quit messing with me.
Didn't she say something about...
being spirited away... or something like that?
Такаги-сан! Answer me!
Такаги-сан!
Why are you screaming? It's just me.
Такаги-сан?!
You were looking for me just now, weren't you?
Huh? Is that what it looked like?
Damn you, Такаги-сан.
This was what you were after.
Hey, over there...
There's a hole.
Why don't you peek inside, Нисиката?
As if I'm gonna fall for the same trick again!
Don't mock me, Такаги-сан!
I-It's stuck! My hand's stuck!
How's my acting ability, Такаги-сан?
Now it's your turn to be scared!
Такаги-сан, it's like something's pulling me.
Help—
Ni-shi-ka-ta...
Did I scare you?
Wh-What is that?
I found it lying on the ground over there.
I'm glad your hand came loose.
Damn it. You just wait,
Такаги-сан. I'll get you this time.
You're way too scared.
We're back out.
Damn... I couldn't retaliate at all.
Hey, look, Onii-тян.
Another couple is on a date in the tunnel!
Shush/ Let's go.
She called it a "date."
What the heck was she was talking about, huh?
Hmm?
Wh-What?
You're blushing.
The test of courage was fun.
Uh... yeah...
It's almost noon. We should head home.
Yeah.
Where are you going, Нисиката?
Huh?
We're going in there again?!
You scared, Нисиката?
O-Of course not!
I met my quota for today.
Wait...
It's summer vacation, yet I still have
as many push-ups to do.
Summer
Science Project
"Summer Science Project."
Yeah, the consommé flavor is quite good.
You're lying. Your're teary-eyed.
No way. Mine's better than
your kelp flavor, Санаэ-тян.
They both sound awful.
There are so many flavors to choose from,
so why in the world would you choose those?
Your watermelon flavor is
playing it too safe, Юкари-тян.
Take risks in life whilst young, right?
Taking risks on popsicle flavors, huh?
Anyway, did you two decide on
subjects for your science projects?
Not yet.
Me neither.
What about you, Мина?
I'm still thinking, too.
Isn't there something easy to do?
Like, something I can finish in a day?
You should do actual research.
How about an observation diary on a dog?
Good idea! That sounds so easy!
They basically behave the same every day,
so all I have to do is copy and paste
and change the dates.
Write it by hand, at least.
Besides, a dog's day consists
of waking up, barking for a walk,
barking to be fed, sleeping,
barking for attention, and
barking to be fed again.
Why bother doing research about that?
You're such a stick-in-the-mud, Юкари-тян.
Well, she is the class president, after all.
She can't help it, I guess.
Right?
Damn these two...
In any case, are you guys doing your homework?
There's still time.
Right?
Just so you know,
you're not copying my work.
Huh?!
I'll do your independent
research for you in return.
On a dog, right? No thanks.
You say that now, but you're gonna
end up sharing your answers with us anyway.
She is the class president, after all.
Right?
Maybe I should do an observation diary on
these two for my independent research.
Water Tap
"Water Tap."
It's hot.
This is the worst day of summer vacation.
No way!
I overslept this morning.
Huh?
And then I had a flat tire.
But it's a good thing it happened on
the day we're not practicing tandem riding.
Такаги-сан said she's
going on a family vacation.
Was she coming back today?
I put off going out during the day
to help do chores around the house,
but they still made me go shopping.
This is the worst summer vacation.
I'll just write that in my one-liner diary.
Huh?
That looks like...
It's Такаги-сан.
She's back already.
All right, I'm gonna follow her.
Maybe I can find a
weakness of some sort.
Did she... I think she saw me just now.
No, maybe it's my imagination.
She noticed me!
But I can see your hat, Такаги-сан.
You're trying to surprise me, aren't you?
Time for a pre-emptive strike!
I'm gonna write that in my one-liner diary.
Sh-She got me!
Going somewhere?
Just grocery shopping...
What a coincidence, me too.
Let's go together. Tandem riding.
Like I said, no tandem riding.
Aww...
When did she find out I was following her?
Then, let's walk together.
Watch out, Такаги-сан!
Are you okay?
Yeah, today is the worst day.
You're hurt.
Ah, no. It's nothing. Just leave it.
No, you should wash it.
How embarrassing...
Does it hurt that much?
No...
It's just that I was already having a bad day,
and now I got injured, too.
I was thinking this is the worst
summer vacation ever.
Jeez... What should I write
for my diary homework?
Here.
Huh?
Uh, it's gonna get dirty.
Don't worry about it.
Th-Thanks...
That feels nice!
You tried to help me, didn't you?
Huh?
Thanks.
You should come in, too.
It's nice and cool.
Huh? No...
Come in already!
Cools you down, huh?
Uh, yeah...
I had a good summer vacation day today.
I got to see a certain somoene today.
Wh-Who?
I'll hand you your souvenir tomorrow.
Hey! Stop that, Такаги-сан, that's cold!