Безответная Любовь
Последний выпуск! 5-ый том
Уже в продаже
The latest issue…
I've been waiting for this.
Покупки
«Shopping.»
Here you go.
Thanks.
I'm going shopping, so let's meet
back here when you're done.
Okay.
Don't get anything too showy.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
The latest issue of 100% Unrequited Love!
What type should I get?
I wonder what type he likes.
I can't wait to get home and read this.
Нисиката.
T-Такаги-сан?!
Why are you so surprised?
Damn it… Why does she always
show up at the worst time?!
Is she following me?!
No… Now's not the time to freak out.
I better make sure she doesn't
find out what I bought!
Anyway, I saw you walk out of the bookstore.
Here it comes!
Did you buy somethi—
Wh-What are you doing here, Такаги-сан?!
That was close.
I have to change the subject
and get through this somehow.
I'm here to shop for a bathing suit.
I see.
A bathing suit?!
You're blushing.
No, it's just that I'm hot!
Hey…
What type of bathing suit do you like, Нисиката?
Wh-What type…?
Uh… Anything is ine.
You're saying you like them all
as long as they're bathing suits?
No! I meant that I really don't care!
Is it that hot?
Yes, it is!
Damn it…
This happens as soon as we meet.
Well, I'll get going now.
Yeah.
I managed to hide
the manga, though.
Can I borrow the 100% Unrequited Love
you just bought sometime?
Такаги-сан, you were watching?!
What are you talking about?
Huh? Isn't that what you got?
No, wait…
There's no way she could have seen
from outside, with where the register is.
She's bluffing.
That was too close.
No, no, no.
Then, what did you buy?
R-Robot Zombie…
How's that?!
You're a girl, so you won't
be interested at all!
Sounds absurd, doesn't it?!
But you actually bought 100%
Unrequited Love, right?
Squeal, squeal!
N-No…
Let me see it, then.
She… She backed me into a corner again.
This is what will always
happens in the end.
Against Такаги-сан, I…
It suddenly occurred to me.
Такаги-сан,
shall we make a bet, then?
Whether the book I bought is
100% Unrequited Love or not.
If you're wrong, you have to something I say.
Okay, but if I get it right, you'll
do what I tell you to do, then.
Yeah, okay…
So, what's your bet?
Your move, Такаги-сан.
My assertive attitude…
should raise doubt in your mind!
Huh?
Нисиката sounds so confident.
Maybe it's not 100% Unrequited Love.
Like so!
If she's gonna find out anyway,
I might as well teach her a lesson!
It won't be the same as last time.
I'm learning every day, too.
Then I'll bet it's 100% Unrequited Love.
Y-You sure you're good with that?
Yeah.
Let's see it.
All right! I got it right.
Why me…?
I should just go home and
read this to comfort me.
I'll be going now.
Where are you going, Нисиката?
Huh?
Help me pick out a bathing suit.
You said if I won, I'd get to
tell you what to do, right?
Bathing suit…?
Are you hot?
Yes, I'm hot!
Купальник
"Bathing Suit."
Which one do you like?
Th-They all look nice.
Will you actually look and choose?
You did lose, Нисиката.
It's embarrassing just being here.
I can't look directly at the bathing suits!
Oh, here.
What about this?
I guess I have to choose
to get this over with.
I… I think it's nice.
Then…
I'll try it on.
Don't go anywhere.
How did it… come to this?
Right now, beyond that curtain…
Такаги-сан is…
What do you think?
D-Dunno.
Okay. I'll try on another one.
You're gonna try on more?!
This may continue
until you say I look good.
That's too cheesy
for me to say!
Нисиката.
Sorry, but can you hand me that bathing suit?
Huh?!
That one on the right.
Такаги-сан… Is she currently…
The one over to the left.
Yeah, that one.
Beyond the curtain, she's currently…
Thanks.
Thank you.
D-Damn it.
That was totally on purpose!
But… I really need to get this over with quickly.
If my classmates see me here,
there's no telling what they'll say.
There are so many.
What about this one?
Такаги-тян!
Мано-тян…
and Накай-кун.
H-Hey…
You're here to buy a bathing suit?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
Ow…
Hey, it's embarrassing being here.
Can you choose one already?
Can't you wait a minute?
I want to buy something I really like.
Let's come back later!
Huh? Why?
Because! See you, Такаги-тян.
Yeah.
Мано-тян and Накай-кун are gone now.
Oh, I see.
You get so shy.
N-No, I don't.
Well then…
Is she trying on some more?
We should decide which one to get soon.
Because you're getting embarrassed.
I said I'm not.
So, which one do you like?
Whatever you like, I guess.
Then how about this one?
Do you think I'll look good?
Yeah…
Then how about this pink one?
This one-piece?
Yeah…
Let's go swimming together next time.
Huh?!
It's a date, then.
Yeah…
I'll buy you juice later. You look hot.
M-Man! It's so hot!
Океан
It's the ocean!
Let's go swimming.
Hurry, hurry!
Ocean
Океан
«Ocean.»
It's the ocean!
It's summer!
Seaweed.
Stop that, Санаэ-тян!
What are you doing, Юкари-тян?
Isn't it obvious? I'm pumping air.
Don't you wanna go for a swim first?
That's why I'm pumping air.
You can't swim?
No wonder you sit out
during the swim lessons.
Never mind me. Just go on ahead.
Shoo. Shoo.
That was quite a swim!
Let's take a break.
What's wrong, Юкари-тян?
Well, the pump broke,
so I was blowing it up on
my own and got winded.
Юкари-тян, are you actually enjoying life?
That's none of your concern!
I'm not going to help you with your
summer vacation homework anymore.
You're on your own.
Please… Please have mercy!
Get off me.
Нисиката, are you making progress on
your summer vacation homework?
Y-Yeah… Somewhat…
Hey, want to do homework together today?
I guess. But I have plans in the afternoon.
let's do our homework until noon, then.
You can copy my answers.
Okay, where should we go? The library?
Oh, but we don't have much time
to go home to get our homework.
It's fine.
We'll just do it at your house.
Huh?
Комната
«Room.»
Нисиката
Oh god…
All of a sudden, Такаги-сан—
a girl—is coming in my room!
Нисиката?
Uh, yeah, can you give me a moment?
Thanks for having me.
There's no need for that.
My parents are at work.
Is this a dream?
Такаги-сан is in my room.
It feels so surreal.
What's wrong?
You were spacing out.
Uh…
It's nothing!
Ah, it's 100% Unrequited Love!
You found me! Squeal!
You have every volumes.
H-Hey, don't look!
S-Sorry…
Why are you apologizing?
Well, because…
You like this, right?
Huh? Huh?!
If you like it, just say so.
Wh-What is this…?
It's just the two of us…
How am I supposed to respond?
Maybe this is a dream!
100% Unrequited Love.
Huh?
You like it, right?
You don't have to hide it.
That's what she was talking about?!
Your room is so you.
Is that a compliment?
Um…
Not really.
But I like it.
W-Want to start studying?
All right.
Oh… But I have only one desk.
Do you have a folding table or anything?
They're all being used in other rooms.
Then should we sit on the same chair?
Huh?!
I'm kidding.
Oh, I know.
Want to study on the bed?
Uh… Um…
See? Turn over the bedding,
and it's a desk.
Is something wrong?
Nice… idea…
Hmm…
Wh-What?
Well, let's start studying.
I'm sitting there, too?!
Uh, um… About what you said earlier…
Yes, of course. It's a promise, after all.
Thanks…
Кандзи: базовые упражнения
Though, I only brought
kanji writing drills.
You tricked me, Такаги-сан!
No, I didn't.
Let's do homework.
Uh… If we're only writing
kanji characters,
did we really need do our homework together?
This is… the situation I saw on
100% Unrequited Love!
Jeez, why do I have to make curry with this guy?!
Кюнко is cranky, cranky.
Oh!
Heart-thump.
H-Hey, let me go.
Why would I let you go?
Come closer.
S-Squeal!
I can't do that!
This is your eraser, huh?
My bad.
Uh, yeah…
Your hand…
S-Sorry!
Are you thirsty?!
Is barley tea okay?
Yeah…
Нейтралитет
Thanks for having me.
All she did was make fun of me, I think.
I'll come again.
She'll come again?
I guess I should clean my room.