Finally...
Finally!
Finally, I got my first cell phone!
Cell Phone
"Cell Phone."
There, I added your number.
Thanks.
Yeah.
You got a cell phone?
Here she comes!
Is that the latest model?
I was thinking of upgrading to that one, too.
Can I see it?
Sure.
Oh, it's pretty light.
I've been waiting for this day.
My plan to tease Takagi-san with my cell phone.
I'll use it... and win against Takagi-san!
Oh, so that's how it works.
Thanks, Nishikata.
No problem.
Huh?
Ah, nothing...
Snacks & Toys        Ramune
Ice Cream
I thought Takagi-san was gonna
ask me for my email address.
What now?
Is something wrong?
Uh, no...
It's nothing.
Damn it...
If I can't contact her, I can't execute my plan.
Why don't I just ask her, then?
Why didn't I think of something
that simple earlier?!
Takagi-san.
What is it?
U-Um...
Y-Your address...
S-Sorry, it's nothing!
Wh-Why?! Why am I so nervous?!
Calm down!
I'm just asking Takagi-san
for her email address!
Am I about to ask a girl
for her email address?!
That's kinda... sorta...
Isn't it?!
Hey, Nishikata.
Is there something you want to ask me?
N-No, no, no!
No, it's nothing! Really!
Hm,
I was certain you wanted to
ask me for my email address.
She knows!
Wait! Isn't this my chance?!
I can get her address just
by answering "yes" right now!
You've gotten careless, Takagi-san.
A-Actually, yeah...
Why did you lie earlier?
Is it because you got embarrassed?
Huh?
D-Damn you, Takagi-san!
N-No... That's not it.
Really?
It's good to have in case something happens.
Like what?
Something.
Who else did you ask?
Kimura, Takao, and Nakai-kun.
And?
I haven't asked that many yet.
Yes, you're right!
You're the first girl I've asked!
So hurry! Just tell me your email address!
You want to text with me?
N-No!
I'm asking for my plan
to tease you by email,
so it's nothing like that, really!
It's nothing weird, I swear!
I knew it was something like that.
Your plan to tease me has been crushed,
but let's exchange email addresses.
Yeah...
"Nishikata"
has been added
"Takagi-san"
As a token of apology for teasing me,
help me clean up next week
when I'm on day duty.
I didn't tease you.
I was about to tease you!
But if I hadn't found out,
you would have, right?
Y-Yeah...
Then it's decided.
But before that...
I'll talk to you when I get home.
Before that?
Does this mean... she's gonna tease
me even when I'm at home, too?
T
Takao
Takagi-san
I want a cell phone.
But when I asked my mom
yesterday, she said I'm too young.
Of course she'll say that when
you ask her out of the blue.
You always say things out of the blue.
That's not true.
I've wanted it for a while now.
For how long?
Umm,
about a week?
So for about three days, then, right?
Either way, it's out of the blue.
What is that?! That's not fair!
That's horrible!
Super Ponpoko!
Pon, pon, pon!
Though, a lot of kids
have one these days.
Maybe I kind of want one, too.
Right?! You want one too, right?!
Let's all ask our moms!
You want one too, right, Sanae-chan?!
No, I don't.
Why not?!
Let's text each other and stuff.
Well, because
I have one already.
How did that happen?!
My parents gave me one since I sometimes
get home late from my club after school.
Oh...
Still, you should've told us.
I know!
If I tell my parents Sanae-chan owns
one, maybe they'll buy one for me!
That's a good idea.
I'm going to tell them that, too.
We're definitely gonna get
ourselves cell phones!
Let's text each other lots!
I wanna play shiritori and word
puzzles until I go to sleep!
Sounds like a pain...
That's probably why your parents
don't want to get you one.
Then let's tell scary stories!
You'll probably drop out first.
I-I'll be fine!
Go ahead. Tell me one now.
One night, you get a call
from an unknown number.
You answer it, only to hear someone moaning.
You quickly hang up and never
get a call from that number again.
That's goo—
But you get curious and call back.
Huh?! Why?!
Only to hear nothing...
What a relief.
However, you get a phone bill
for a hundred thousand yen.
Fake invoices are scary!
You're scarier, Yukari-chan!
Horror
"Horror."
Morning, Nishikata.
Morning.
You kept your promise from before.
Yeah...
Let me help.
Thanks.
You look tired.
Not really...
Were you up late watching a
recording of 100% Unrequited Love?
No!
Really?
What, then?
Nothing special...
Were you texting your classmates?
Y-Yeah, I guess...
About what?
Huh?
It's unusual for Takagi-san
to be this curious.
This is...
It's so fun to texting people when you
get your very first cell phone, huh?
I was hooked, too.
And then you end up getting in trouble.
Someone who exchanges
messages with Takagi-san...
Who is it?
O-Oh, a girl from our class?
Nope.
Calm yourself. Something
like this happened before.
The last time I went tandem riding,
it was with my dad.
I know! Your dad?
Why would I do that with my dad?
T-Touché...
Curious?
Not really...
If you tell me what you text about
with the boys, I'll tell you.
I don't care.
Wait. I can kill two birds with one stone.
Your fun stops here, Takagi-san!
Actually,
we were sharing funny videos yesterday.
Like what?
Yes, it's working.
Email
Takagi-san
The link Kimura sent me...
I couldn't sleep well, thanks to this.
Did you send me something?
Yeah, a video of a cute animal.
It's not a perverted site, is it?
It's not!
Let's see.
It's so scary that you're at
a loss for words, aren't you, Takagi-san?
Nishikata.
What is it, Takagi-san?
Is this something you always look at?
Wh-Why?!
Hold on. What is that?!
That's not what I sent.
Huh?
Just thought I'd ask.
Now then, let's see what
Nishikata sent me.
Sh-She got me again! Damn it!
It really is an animal video.
That's cute. Is it a goat?
Good, good. She's let her guard down.
It's gonna start soon.
Yes, go! Cower in fear, Takagi-san!
Hmm...
Scary.
Huh?!
Uh... Isn't it scary?
It's scary, but
it's not that scary when you
watch it in the morning.
She has a point.
So this is the kind of
stuff you guys are into.
Boys are funny.
H-How about you? What do
you talk about and with whom?
I talk about normal stuff.
That's not an answer!
It's not?
Umm, I talk with someone that starts with an "I."
I? I...
I... Ishii-san?
Wrong.
After "I" is "To."
Ito... Itou?
Huh? Itou? That boy?
No, it's not Itou-kun from our class.
Last is "Ko."
Itou... Ko?
Huh?
(Itoko = cousin)
Huh? What?
Ninety-seven, ninety-eight,
ninety-nine...
Damn you, Takagi-san.
I thought I could get back at her today,
but I got defeated yet again.
No, the day's not over yet.
If it didn't work in the morning,
I'll just send one to her at night.
An even scarier video Kimura
told me about after school today.
It's scary, so I didn't watch, but...
This will surely—
Takagi-san
Takagi-san?
I have a feeling I'm gonna have
to do more push-ups after this
Hello, Nishikata?
Yeah...
I thought it was almost time.
F-For what?
For you to send me a scary video.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You think I'm gonna reveal
my plan just like that?
The battle is—
Just you wait after you hang up the phone...
Is that what you were thinking?
N-No... I wasn't.
Really?
Really...
Then, are you going to sleep soon?
Uh, yeah... Probably...
I see.
I was just about to, too.
This feels kind of strange.
It's the first time I'm talking to you at night.
It kind of makes my heart flutter.
See you tomorrow, then. Good night.
Uh... Good night...
Nishikata?
Wh-What?
You aren't hanging up yet?
Huh?
The phone.
You hang up first.
I called you, so you hang up.
Why?
Then, let's hang up together.
Okay.
One, two,...
Liar.
Y-You, too!
Man... I can't sleep tonight, either.
Picture
"Picture."
It's a cat fight.
Wait here, Takagi-san.
What are you going to do?
Okay, good. Stay right there.
All right! A picture-perfect moment!
Damn... I only got the wall.
What's with the photos all of the sudden?
I'm competing with the guys right now
to see who can take the best picture.
Who's in the lead right now?
This one by Kimura is unbeatable.
Ah...
Super
Ponpoko
That's intense.
A funny picture, huh?
Takagi-san! Let me take
a picture of your funny face!
Huh?
I can totally beat Super Ponpoko!
If you'll do anything I ask, it's a deal.
Anything?
Anything means anything.
Scary!
She has what it takes for me to win.
Oh, Nishikata...
Takagi-san! That face!
I just gave you a photo opportunity.
O-One more time!
No can do.
Wait, this is Takagi-san, after all.
She enjoys this too much.
She'll want to do it again!
I'll just act as though I'm upset, and...
Nishikata.
I knew it! Here's my chance!
A toy snake?
That's a good picture.
You took my picture?!
H-Hey, delete that!
No way. It's a great picture.
I'll delete it if you'll do anything I ask.
Damn you, Takagi-san! Such a cheap shot!
I got such a great picture.
Wanna see?
No, I don't.
See, see?
Burst mode?!
Cool, huh?
The way your face changes...
Damn you, Takagi-san!
I know!
I'll take a picture of her laughing
with her mouth wide open.
She'll be embarrassed for sure.
Huh?!
Do I look okay?
We're even now.
We're not even at all!
I-I'll delete this, so you delete yours, too.
Nope, I'm not deleting it.
So you don't have to delete my picture, either.
No, that's not the point.
See ya.
Yeah...
She's in a great mood.
But I didn't get a single funny picture.
Nishikata,
don't show my picture to anyone.
It's embarrassing.
No way. I can't show this to anyone!
What will people say?!
It's dangerous! Delete, delete...
She did say it's embarrassing.
Maybe I can use it for some kind of deal.
I guess I'll keep it.