Isn't there a way to get the
last word against Takagi-san?
I can't just let her keep
teasing me like this every day.
S-Sorry!
Oh, Nishikata.
Morning.
Oh, ah... morning...
Is something wrong?
No, nothing...
Let's go to school together.
O-Okay...
Who's Taller?
"Who's Taller?"
Did she see that?
Did she see what just happened?
Nishikata.
Wh-What?
Do you want to tandem ride?
No. We'll get in trouble if someone sees us.
You're just embarrassed.
That's not it.
Okay, okay.
It doesn't seem like she saw
me bump into the utility pole.
Phew...
You finally changed into
your winter uniform, too.
Yeah, it's been cold lately,
so I thought it was time.
Hmm...
Wh-What?
Did you get taller?
Huh?
I think that uniform looked
a little bigger on you last spring.
She's right.
Right now,
it feels like the uniform fits just right!
Could it be... that I'm having a growth spurt?
I'm growing so much, it kind of sucks.
I wonder if this is what
people call a "growth spurt"?
But you haven't changed much, Takagi-san.
That's sexual harassment.
Huh?!
"Haven't changed much"...
N-No!
Th-That's not what I was talking about.
I-I was talking about height.
Eh? I was talking about height, too.
What did you think I meant?
N-Nothing...
What?
Never mind. Maybe you haven't
grown that much taller.
Huh?
No, no, I did grow!
I'm probably taller than
you right now, Takagi-san!
Then let's see who's taller.
Why here?
We can't tell with our shoes on, right?
We're gonna be late for school.
It'll be quick. Here, turn around.
Let's see...
It's kinda... warm.
Um, Takagi-san.
Don't you normally stand
against a wall and put a mark?
It's more accurate if we
stand together like this.
We're about the same height, I think.
Huh? Really?!
Why don't you check it out yourself?
You're right.
Right?
You're not on your tiptoes, are you?
You don't trust me?
Then...
If we face each other, you'll
know if I'm cheating.
All right, then...
It-It kinda looks like... I'm taller.
I was on my tiptoes earlier.
So you were cheating! You liar!
I didn't say I wasn't.
Good for you, you won.
Takagi-san, you're acting
all cool on the outside,
but on the inside, I bet you're really bitter.
Oh, and by the way, I'm not bitter.
Huh?
Well, when you grow bigger,
you run into utility poles and stuff,
and that seems painful.
Y-You saw that?
Let's go to school.
Takagi-san.
Hey, Takagi-san?
So cold...
Is it that cold?
You're so sensitive
to the cold, Yukari-chan.
Take that.
Mina, your hand is so cold!
I Hate the Cold
"I Hate the Cold"
Jeez...
If you do that again, I won't forgive you.
Touch.
Stop it!
Why are your hands so cold?!
Yukari-chan,
People who have cold hands...
have warm hearts!
I don't think a person with a warm
heart would do what you just did.
Now, now, don't hold a grudge.
Hey, if you do it again, I'll be really mad.
You're already mad.
Touch.
So cold! Hey!
Stop that, Sanae-chan!
"My heart is so warm" attack...
Help me, Yukari-chan!
Take that!
That's for what you guys did earlier!
Huh?
Yukari-chan, your hand is warm.
You must have a cold heart.
Why would you say that?!
Don't come near me, you cold-hearted person!
"My heart is so cold" attack!
Take that!
That's cold!
What did you do that for?!
You can get back at me.
Stop that!
There's no way I can do that!
Take that!
I said stop! It's cold!
A person with cold hands has a warm heart.
Not true!
Takagi-chan and Nishikata-kun...
They came to school together today.
They're so close.
Maybe they are going out.
Invitation
"Invitation."
I wonder if Nishikata-kun and
Takagi-chan are going out.
Who knows?
You're not interested?
They seem really close.
Yukari, are you jealous?
No, uh... It's not that I'm jealous, but...
Wipe your hands with a
towel after washing!
Mina, Yukari says she wants
a boy to flirt with!
That's not what I said!
Mina, are you listening?
Mina?
Jeez, Sanae-chan, don't talk to me right now!
I was just about to pee, but now I can't!
Huh?
You're too much, Sanae.
You should watch it. It's fun.
Really? I'll watch it, then.
Takagi-chan.
Year 1 Class 2
I just came up with the ultimate plan!
It's the ultimate, fail-proof plan
to tease Takagi-san
on our way home from school!
What are you smirking about, Nishikata?
Something pervy?
I-It's nothing like that!
Nothing like what?
Wh-What I meant was...
You're blushing.
Damn you, Takagi-san. Just wait...
By the way, Nishikata...
do you want to
walk home together today?
Oh, sure!
Oh, no! Did she realize I'm up to something?
Yeah, sure.
Why did you repeat yourself?
No reason, really.
You might change your mind after school,
so you can give me a definite answer then.
See ya.
What was that about?
As long as she isn't onto me, I guess.
Hey, Nishikata.
We're playing "Super-Pro" at my
house today. You wanna join us?
Sorry, I can't today.
What? Is it your girlfriend again?
"Girlfriend"?!
It's Takagi-san, right?
Huh?! What are you talking about?!
We're not like that.
Takagi-chan and Nishikata-kun
are not going out.
We asked her in the restroom earlier!
Really?
Yeah!
Oh, now I wanna pee.
Restroom, restroom...
Then what was she doing in the restroom earlier?
That aside, Nishikata,
if you're not going out with Takagi-san,
why are you walking home with her?
Well, she asked me.
Isn't that because you two are going out?
Uh,
I don't think so.
Well, whatever.
Hey, isn't next period in the science room?
Crap, let's hurry!
Yeah.
No, I think... Takagi-san just wants to tease me.
Which character are you going to play?
Let's go home.
Hiromitsu, I guess.
We're going straight home today.
Huh?!
I want a Ponkan Popsicle!
You want a popsicle in this
freezing weather?
Eating a popsicle in the kotatsu is the best!
You said it.
She wants an answer,
so that means she wants me to ask her, right?
That's kinda embarrassing.
I've never been the one to ask her
to walk home with me before.
Nishikata.
Wh-What is it, Takagi-san?!
Oh, good! If Takagi-san asks,
all I have to say is yes.
Someone asked me today if
I was going out with you.
Huh?
And they think I'm the one
who's in love with you.
Do you think it's because I'm always the one
asking you to walk home together?
Damn you, Takagi-san! So
this was what you were after!
You created a situation
where I have to ask you
just so you can enjoy watching me squirm!
Something wrong?
Try to sound calm.
Like, "Oh, really?"
O-Oh, r-really?
Good!
Anyway, about your request from this morning...
I-I don't have any plans, so...
So, let's...
"Let's"?
Hang in there, me!
If I get through this, I can tease Takagi-san!
Let's...
walk home together.
Let me think.
Huh?!
Just kidding. Let's go home.
I can't wait,
It looks like you're scheming something.
She knows?!
If she knows, should I not execute my plan?
But I came up with such a good idea.
I haven't even thought of how to carry
out the plan to begin with, though.
Want to buy juice?
Yeah, I'm parched.
Wow, most of them are sold out.
I wanted something cold, but all they have is
Delicious Sweet Red Bean Soup
Hot
sweet red bean soup
Cold
Wormwood Juice
and some weird stuff!
Which one?
I have a feeling I'll regret it
no matter what I choose!
"I'll regret it no matter what I choose"?
Should we find another vending machine?
Ah, nah...
I'm thirsty, so I guess...
Ugh... Gross...
You couldn't tell from
the way it looked?
I completely regret getting this!
But now I can carry out my plan!
Hey, Takagi-san.
Let's say one juice is really
tasty but gives you a fever,
and the other juice is just plain disgusting.
Which would you choose?
Two-Choice Question
"Two-Choice Question."
A very tasty juice that gives you a fever,
or a juice that's plain disgusting, huh?
How about it, Takagi-san?
You can't choose, can you?
Feel the unease, and let me see that
uneased face of yours, Takagi-san!
Nishikata.
If I drink the tasty juice and get
a fever, will you come visit me?
Huh? D-Does that have anything
to do with your answer?
Significantly.
You wouldn't come and see me?
I-If you had a fever, I guess I'd go visit you.
Then I choose the tasty one.
Oh...
Huh?
This is weird. What is this?
Takagi-san isn't troubled at all.
The only one troubled here... is me?
The "two-choice question" plan has failed.
No, no! It's too early to give up!
Next question, then!
Okay.
No allowance for life, or no more teasing me!
No allowance for life.
That was fast!
I've been saving up my New Year's money,
so I'd be fine for a while.
Once I enter high school,
I'll just start a part-time job.
So I'd rather keep teasing you.
I underestimated her!
I have to ask a better question!
Nishikata.
Huh?
You've been asking weird questions,
but are you trying to give me a hard time?
No, not really...
I'll ask you a question this time, then.
Would you rather me disappear
or continue to be teased by me forever?
Which would you choose?
"Disappear"?
I'd be gone.
Huh?
I don't want to be teased,
but for her to disappear?
That's kinda...
I'd choose to be teased.
So you do like to be teased, huh?
No, of course not!
But... you disappearing
is not really what I want.
You mean you want to be with me?
That's not...
You're blushing!
Damn you, Takagi-san!
Is it that fun to see me squirm?
I have to come up
with a really good question!
Next question.
We're still doing this?!
Getting a zero on all your tests for life,
or kissing me.
Which would you choose?
Huh?!
K-Ki—
Which one?
Getting a zero, even if I study?
Yep. A zero no matter what you do.
There's no way.
That'll mean I'll never get any more
allowance, and I can't even enter high school!
But if I choose the kiss,
she'll definitely make fun of me!
Can't choose, huh?
Damn... The more I struggle to choose,
the happier she looks!
I have to choose quickly!
Getting a zero on the tests is too much! But...!
I have no choice!
Th-Then, the one that doesn't
get me a zero on the test.
Which one would that be?
Th-The one with the kiss...
I see. Okay, then.
Huh?!
Oh, so you are.
You're a little taller than me.
What's wrong, Nishikata?
I was just seeing who's taller.
She's made fun of me so many times today.
But I have this all figured out now.
On option has to be
something she'd never choose,
and the other is simply to make fun of her.
That way, I'll definitely win!
Takagi-san, the next questio—
Then, next question.
Huh?!
Go around the campus doing
a handstand, or the two of us—
H-Hold on! I can't do a handstand!
And, like, when can I ask the questions?!
You have to answer my question first.
B-But...