How to approach a cat.
Number one: Don't make eye contact.
Number two: Crouch down.
How about it? Now you know
I don't mean you any harm, right?
Number three:
Approach slowly.
This is amazing!
I can get so close now, following
the advice on that show yesterday!
Hey, it's Nishikata.
What were you doing?
N-Nothing...
Cat
"Cat."
Damn you, Takagi-san!
I was so close to touching that cat!
But...
I'm glad she didn't see me petting the cat.
If she did...
Nishikata's petting a cat!
You're a boy, but you like cute things, huh?
That's definitely what would have happened.
There's no way I'm gonna give her
more fodder to make fun of me with!
Oh, a cat.
Where?!
You like cats?
N-Not really...
Crap! I messed up.
There.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Come here.
You're naïve, Takagi-san.
Cats are very wary animals.
There's no way that cat will—
Oh, here he comes.
What?!
Why?! That wasn't even a proper call!
Could Takagi-san be a cat master?!
Good boy. You're cute as usual, Meeta.
You know this cat?
Yep. He belongs to the
old lady by our house.
No wonder. I freaked out for nothing.
Good boy.
He really likes people.
He lets you pet him all you want.
Pet him all you want?!
An all-you-can-pet cat?!
That's amazing!
Why don't you try, Nishikata?
Huh?! Why?!
You were trying to pet that cat earlier, right?
You were trying to use
that trick from TV yesterday.
You like cats, right?
Sh-She already knows!
I-I was just trying to test
out that trick from TV.
So you don't particularly like cats or anything?
I guess not.
It's not as if I've ever had the urge
to touch a cat or anything.
Oh, really?
They're so cute, though.
Their coats are so fluffy,
and their paws are so squishy.
This cat even lets people to touch his paws?!
I-I want to touch it.
But no! It's too late to say that now!
I know!
I really don't understand people
who want to touch cats.
Are they that cute?
And even if they are,
I wouldn't want to pet them.
They're animals, after all.
You don't know what they might do.
Are you just saying that because
you're scared of getting scratched?
She took the bait!
Of course not!
All right, I'll prove to you right now
that I'm not scared of petting cats!
I see. I'm sorry I doubted you.
Huh?!
I believe you.
Your face is like an open book, Nishikata!
You really want to pet the cat, don't you?
Damn you, Takagi-san!
Well? Are you going to pet him or not?
Can I... pet him?
Yeah.
Though Meeta is gone.
He's gone already?!
Do you want to go look for a cat, Nishikata?
We're gonna be late for school.
Satou-chan likes Tanaka-kun from Class 3.
Yeah, I can kinda tell!
I want to talk about love, too!
Taste
"Taste."
Year 1 Class 2
So guys,
what's your type, anyway?
Was that too abrupt?!
I like the dependent type.
Whoa?!
I like a large physique and long hair.
O-Oh? I didn't expect that.
We can do this! These two are ready!
We were just talking about that right now.
Huh?! R-Really?
They've grown so much.
All right, I'm going to dig more in-depth.
What's your type, Yukari-chan?
I'm glad you asked!
I like long legs and the
handsome type, I guess...
What about hair?
Sanae is particular about a guy's hair.
I like it long, too, I guess.
This is fun!
This is the kind of conversation
I've wanted to have with my friends!
A borzoi, then.
Yep, yep. A borzoi...
Wh-What are you talking about?
We're talking about dogs, right?
So what do you like?
I like chihuahuas.
Huh? You're contradicting what you said earlier.
Though, there are long-haired chihuahuas.
Portrait
"Portrait."
Aren't you going to draw?
You're going to run out of time.
Yeah...
Why does it have to be a portrait?
Can't we just draw whatever we want?
The importance of a smile
Nishikata, are you actually looking
at me while you're drawing?
I am looking.
Listen up.
You can get too focused on drawing
and take more time drawing
than actually observing the subject,
but that's not gonna work.
You have to observe.
Take twice as much
time observing as drawing.
You got that?
I-I guess so.
Wh-What?
Sorry, it's nothing.
What? What was that laugh about?
Is there something on my face?
No, there was nothing when I checked
in the restroom mirror during the break.
What, then? Bed head?
No, that can't be it, either.
Could it be?! My face itself?!
I can't do anything about that!
Calm down. I have to calm down.
I know. It's the usual stuff.
She's just making me worry
so she can enjoy my reaction.
Damn Takagi-san!
Two can play this game!
Are you laughing because
your drawing sucks so bad?
No!
Then, is there something on my face?
I didn't expect her to ask me straight.
N-No...
No damage...
I told you, Mina!
My eyes don't slant upward so much.
That's how I envision you, though.
Don't draw me based on
your "envisioning"! Observe!
That's it!
Huh? This is me?
Well, that how I envision you.
That's what I'll say.
Ten more minutes.
Okay, this looks good.
Nishikata,
can I take a look?
Yeah, go ahead.
How's that, Takagi-san?
Crap, did I go too far?
U-Uh, I drew it based on how I envision you.
Nishikata.
What the heck?! Takagi-san, your face!
My stomach hurts!
If you're going to draw me weird,
you might as well make it really weird.
Here, look closely.
Okay...
Can you see me well? I can
get closer if you want.
N-No, you're fine.
Good.
On a closer look,
Takagi-san is... p—
Pre— Pret—
There, finished.
See?
What do you think?
Was I looking sideways that much?
Oh, I forgot.
Huh?
Finished.
My face isn't that red!
You've been blushing the whole time.
No, I haven't! It just looks like that.
Look carefully! How am I blushing?!
House of Fortune
Fortune Telling
"Fortune Telling."
Oh, this card means your wish
will more or less come true.
Really?
Why don't you get your
love fortune telling done, too, Mina?
She's good.
Do it.
You say that, but I bet you're the one
who wants to get a reading, Yukari-chan.
No, I don't!
You're so obvious.
It's for Mina!
What a pain... I wanted to go home.
Nishikata.
Takagi-san.
Hey, Nishikata,
let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Why?
The loser has to buy juice
on the way home. How about it?
Uh, sorry, but I have to clean up after school,
so go home without me.
I'll wait until you're done, then.
No, I'd feel bad.
Then, if you win, I'll help you clean up.
Why do you wanna do
rock-paper-scissors so badly?
Don't worry about it.
I guess it's okay.
Wait!
What?
No psychological attacks like declaring
what you're gonna go with!
Okay, I'm good with that.
That was close. I lost to her
four times in a row before.
Ready?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I-I won?!
My first victory over Takagi-san.
Yes! I did it!
I bet she's super mad!
I'll help you, then.
She doesn't seem to mind.
In any case, I won.
I'm gonna drown myself in
euphoria over my first triumph.
Nishikata.
What is it, Takagi-san?
Do you believe in fortune telling?
Fortune telling? N-No, why?
We were all doing it today.
Oh, like with the deck of cards earlier?
They're tarot cards.
I had my tarot reading about love today.
Oh...
Love?
I was told I'll do well with my current crush.
Current crush? I-I see.
Nishikata, do you have a crush?
Huh? What?
I said, do you have a crush?
N-No! I don't!
I see.
Why did she ask me that just now?
Could it be? Does Takagi-san...
like me?
What's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Why am I so nervous?
Huh?
Does this mean...
I like... Takagi-san?
N-No, that can't be.
Oh, by the way, Nishikata.
Wh-What?!
I asked whether you have a crush
because I had your tarot reading done, too.
S-So that's why.
I see.
Wait, am I disappointed.
As it turns out, you'll do well
with your crush, too.
You wish you had a crush now, don't you?
You're blushing.
That's because I'm hard at work cleaning.
I-I should change the subject.
What other readings did you have done?
Um...
Like, what your choice was going to be
for rock-paper-scissors.
Huh? You mean the
rock-paper-scissors I won earlier?
Yeah.
See? It's just fortune telling, after all.
I feel stupid for worrying.
That's what you get for
believing in fortune telling.
You're stuck cleaning.
It came true.
Huh? But I won.
Yeah, you did.
Huh?
Let's clean up, Nishikata.
Uh,
yeah... Huh?
Nishikata has appeared!
Toy with
Soothe
Run
Tease
Takagi-san
Nishikata has appeared!
Nishikata looks embarrassed.
Critical
Takagi-san teases him.
Critical hit!
"Critical."
Nishikata has been defeated!
Nishikata still looks embarrassed.
I'll finally win against
Takagi-san today, for sure!
Oh, Nishikata.
Morning.
You're in a good mood today.
Really? You think so?
You're right, though.
You have no idea what's coming, Takagi-san.
I'm invincible today.
Because according to
this morning's horoscope, I—
Is it because Cancer was number
one in the morning horoscope?
How do you know I'm a Cancer?!
Don't you remember me
wishing you a happy birthday?
Oh, yeah. Now that you mention it.
Why does she even know
about the horoscope?
I have to be careful.
But you underestimate me, too.
I bet you don't know that in
today's blood-type fortune, I—
Also, blood type O got number one too, right?
How do you know I'm type O?!
Oh, so you are. I had a feeling.
She's too good.
I was the one underestimating her.
You can't mess with Takagi-san.
But just you wait.
Today, I am—
You have an invincible aura
because you got number
one in both fortunes, huh?
Well, I hope something good happens today.
Y-Yeah...
Just watch, Takagi-san.
I'm lucky as hell today!
I was teased fifty times today, so
I have to do a hundred and fifty push-ups!
Wh-Why?! Damn it!
Was I stupid for getting excited
just because I was told I have good fortune?
Are you upset because
nothing special happened?
It's just a fortune.
You had a tarot reading, too.
Man, I've been thinking of a plan
to win against Takagi-san all day,
but nothing came to mind.
Maybe I should just give up today.
Or was today a good day
because that's all that happened?
Is that what it means?
Hey, Nishikata, let's walk home together.
Yeah, okay...
No, I can't let it end like this!
By the way, what did it say about your fortune?
Huh? Oh, you mean the one-line description?
Yeah.
Uh, let's see.
Cancer is in first place.
You'll land a critical hit!
Get 'em!
That's right! A critical hit!
Which means I'll have a chance
to turn the tables with a single blow!
I get it now! No matter how
many times she teases me,
If I get to tease her just once, I win!
Don't give up!
So? What did it say?
Uh, I wonder what it said.
Hey, Nishikata.
The Fierce-Soccer
video game is on sale today.
Let's play at this kid's house!
Fierce-Soccer...
I wanted to play, too.
No! I can't go home
without scoring my critical hit!
But then again, I have
yet to come up with a plan.
No, I should be able to!
I'm the luckiest man
of the day, after all.
You're okay with not playing?
Hm?
The video game?
Uh, yeah...
I wanted to walk home with you, anyway.
Hmm... There must be something.
Wait! Did I just say something
super awkward just now?
T-Today's fortune said I'd land
a critical hit, so I...
I thought I'd finally win against you!
So I didn't mean what you think!
Damn it! This is not a critical hit!
I just made an own goal!
So pretend you didn't hear that.
I guess I can do that.
I'll pretend I didn't hear
it if you say it again.
Why would I?!
I-I'm going this way.
Bye-bye!
A critical hit...
Terrifying.