Sanae-chan!
Here.
For you.
To Sanae-chan
What's this?
A love letter?
No way! It's a normal letter.
Everyone's doing it these days.
Didn't you know?
No.
Sheesh.
I'll write one for you later, too, Yukari-chan.
I appreciate it, but you should focus on
studying while you're in class, Mina.
Friendship is more important than studying.
Is there a letter-writing trend
among the girls right now?
Looks like it.
Imagine if they're writing love letters, too.
They get pretty intense
when it comes to writing.
I know.
Love letters, huh?
They could just say things out loud.
Why would they bother to write letters?
They must have a ton of time to waste.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Come on, Sanae. He's had enough.
One kick is enough.
But kicking him once is okay?
Year 1 Class 2
We're starting class.
Open your textbooks to page 76.
Takagi-san's doing letters, too?
I guess Takagi-san's just an ordinary girl, too.
What?
Letter
"Letter."
What's wrong, Nishikata?
N-Nothing at all!
A letter? Who's it from?
Why me?
Imagine if they're writing love letters, too.
No, no, no, that's impossible!
Someone's playing a prank on me.
Oh, yeah!
This might be Takagi-san's doing.
No, it must be her.
Takagi-san...
Wait a second.
What if it's someone else?
What if it isn't Takagi-san?
If she finds out I got a letter,
she's going to tease me again.
Yes, Nishikata?
No...
The weather's so nice today.
Are you hiding something?
Of course not.
Something's suspicious, though.
You're red, too.
Y-You're imagining things.
That's fine,
but why do you have your textbook closed?
W-Well, you see...
Does it have something to do
with your face being red?
It's nothing!
And my face isn't red!
Is there really nothing?
There really isn't!
I guess I was imagining things.
Oh, and the letter in your textbook...
I put that there.
I knew it!
I totally knew that. Of course.
Liar.
I was actually having fun making you squirm.
Aren't you going to read what's inside?
You wrote something?
Obviously.
You're teasing me again, aren't you?
Why aren't you saying anything?!
O-Okay, I'll read it at home.
Read it now.
Wh-Why?
School's out after this class, right?
I want an answer by then.
A-An answer?
If it's a letter that needs an answer,
it's a letter asking a question.
So it's not just something to tease me?
Imagine if they're writing love letters, too.
S-So it could be a love letter?!
Wait, could it be?!
Is it a love letter by any chance?
The silent treatment again?!
Aren't you going to read it?
I-I will. I'll read it.
I just have to read it, right?
That means whatever is written
in it is just to tease me.
So no matter whatever it says,
I have to be firm so she doesn't tease me.
I have to be bold.
But if...
It really can't be possible.
But if it's a love letter...
If it is, I...
Dear Nishikata,
Let's walk home together today.
—Takagi
You could have just asked me directly.
Letter-writing is popular right now.
Besides, I wanted to see how you would react.
So you were teasing me!
Ow!
Shut it, Nishikata!
First Day of School
"First Day of School."
Entrance Ceremony
Staff Office
Thanks a lot, man.
Not at all. Pardon me.
Oh yeah.
What's your name, new kid?
Me?
I'm Nishikata.
Nishikata-kun.
Congratulations on getting in.
Right.
Tanabe
You're going to be learning with
each other over the next year.
I'm not going to force you to
get along no matter what.
But keep in mind that you should
try your best to make things work.
Did I lose it somewhere?
Well, I don't want to start the
year with a long speech, so...
Slept in already?
No, I...
I'll commend you for having balls.
No...
What's your name?
Nishikata.
All right. Sit down.
Yes, sir.
Everyone's looking at me.
I have to get to know people
and clear things up
before I become known as the late guy.
Tanabe-sensei, a moment.
The car is late.
It's late, huh?
So the entrance ceremony is, too?
Thanks for your understanding.
I just got word that the entrance
ceremony is behind schedule.
It seems it's going to take a while,
so in the meantime...
We're figuring out seating.
Oh, come on.
I'm in the far back corner.
Normally I'd be happy, but
it doesn't benefit me at all right now.
I don't even know anyone as it is.
There's no one behind me or to my left.
Worse, I'm sitting next to a girl.
Did you actually sleep in?
She's talking to me.
You were about to say
something to the teacher.
Y-Yeah...
No, actually, well...
If only I'd made it on time...
I made it to school on time, but...
It's all because of that Takagi-san person.
All right, everyone, head to the gymnasium.
Keep quiet. Don't run.
Okay.
Hey.
Let's go together.
Wait a moment.
You will soon have a great treasure,
known as the right to vote.
It is important to choose
politicians who are worthy of trust.
Congratulations, New Students
Likewise, to your mother and father...
That was such a long speech.
Wasn't it?
That old dude was talking forever.
It's the same thing in middle
school as it was in elementary.
You're pretty awesome, though,
coming in late on the first day.
No, I...
Quit yapping and take your seats.
Huh?
Sorry I'm late.
Take your seat.
That's it for today, but classes start tomorrow.
Don't get giddy because it's the
entrance ceremony. Go straight home.
Hey, Nishikata-kun...
Want me to guess why you were late today?
If I can guess on my first try, I win.
Sure.
Wait, how is she going
to guess on her first try?
You were delivering a lost item.
What?! How?!
Yo, shut up, Nishikata.
Sorry.
How?
I wonder how?
Takagi-san?
You weren't there during
the self-introductions.
Why are you reacting like that?
Hey! Quiet down over there!
Sorry.
Thanks for picking it up.
Nice to meet you.
Seating Arrangement
"Seating Arrangement."
Seventy-two, seventy-three,
seventy-four, seventy-five.
It's getting there.
Status Quo
Ow...
She's not here yet.
Morning, Nishikata.
Morning, Takagi-san.
Have you heard, Nishikata?
There's a seating arrangement change today.
When?
During homeroom.
Homeroom?
That's first period.
Taka—
What's wrong?
Oh, really?
That'll be fun.
Yeah?
No, I mean, we haven't had
a seating change in a while.
Well, I guess it could be fun in some ways.
I wanted to be next to you for
a while longer, though.
She's going to tease me again.
Close one.
Lots
Does everyone have a lot?
All right, move your desks
according to your lots.
Nishikata, what number?
Twenty-nine.
Ah.
The far back again, then.
What about you?
I'm front and center.
Oh.
We're going to be pretty far.
Yeah.
Bye.
Yay!
Give me answers during tests, Yukari-chan.
No, that's straight-up cheating.
It's called mutual aid.
So what are you going to help me with, then?
I'll cheer for you from behind.
Hey, Nishikata.
Are you here?
No, over there.
Aww.
Too bad we aren't closer.
Yeah.
My vision's gotten bad lately.
I hope I can see the chalkboard.
Oh, I'm next to Nishikata-kun.
Mano-san?
Oh, I see.
What's with that reaction?
It's nothing. Don't mind me.
I'm just depressed because
I don't get to be by Nakai-kun.
Nakai-kun?
Hey.
Someone!
Someone please switch seats with me!
How am I supposed to eat lunch early
if I'm in front of the teacher's podium?!
You aren't switching seats unless
you have a legitimate reason.
Also, Kimura, I'll see you
at the staff office later.
In front of the teacher's podium?
I wanted to be next to you for
a while longer, though.
K-Kimura-kun,
I have bad eyesight. Let's switch.
Nope, I already had someone switch.
I don't care.
Nishikata.
Hey.
Huh?
I'm sitting here now.
Why?
Nakai-kun switched with Kimura-kun
because he couldn't see the chalkboard.
Nakai-kun came to the front,
and Mano-chan wanted to switch
with me, since I was next to him.
Mano-chan's small, so she prefers the front.
I-I see.
Nishikata, you tried to sit
next to me, didn't you?
No, I couldn't see the chalkboard.
Yeah?
I swear!
Class is starting. Get your textbooks out.
Oh yeah, what were you about to say?
It looked like you've been wanting
to say something since this morning.
Sorry it took a while to return this to you.
Thanks.
From summer break?
Yeah, and...
And from the first day of school?
You remembered?
You remembered, too, huh?
Yeah.
Thanks.
I washed it well.
No...
I'm glad, though.
Hm?
Oh, stuff.
That I got to return your handkerchief,
and that we're next to each other again.
No, I mean, you know.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah.
Dear Takagi-san,
Thank you.
—Nishikata